

ARJUN A ACHARRY UI DESIGN

My Contact

arjunaacharry007@gmail.com

+91 86067 94034

Pathanamthitta , Kerala

arjunaacharry.github.io

Education

Mahatma Gandhi University

Bachelor of Computer Application (BCA), (Kristu Jyoti College of Management and Technology, Changanacherry) 2022 - Present

Directorate of Higher Secondary Education (DHSE)

Computer Science (CS), (NSS Higher Secondary School, Kunnamthanam) 2020 - 2022

Skills

- Graphic Design
- UI Design
- Adobe Photoshop
- Flgma
- Canva
- · Adobe Illustrator
- HTML/CSS
- Communication

About Me

As a dedicated learner with a passion for UI design, I am currently pursuing a degree in Computer Application from Kristu Jyoti College of Management and Technology while also taking online courses to further enhance my skills and knowledge. My goal is to gain valuable experiences in the fields of UI design and cybersecurity, with the ambition of securing a responsible position in an organization where I can apply my capabilities and expertise to contribute to the success of the team.

Through my dedication to continual learning and passion for UI design, I am confident in my ability to excel in a professional setting and make a valuable contribution to any organization.

Experience

Freelance Graphic Design

2021 - Present

Key responsibilities:

- Designing and creating visual content
- Understanding client requirements
- Presenting design concepts
- Making revisions
- · Delivering final design files

Graphic Designer | Cybernetix, (Cyber club of our college)

2022 - Present

Key responsibilities:

- Designing and creating visual content
- · Understanding program requirements
- · Presenting design concepts
- Making revisions
- Delivering final design files

Freelance UI Design

2022 - Present

Kev responsibilities:

- Designing User Interfaces
- Staying Up-to-Date with Design Trends
- Creating Style Guides
- Conducting Usability Testing